[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 7, "question": "But sometimes if it wasn't for the strap, what would this world be like today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 8, "answer": "On what he missed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "Did you ever hope that he would find true love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "I always thought about that, but Michael seemed happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "What I'm struck by, I love this picture, Katherine which is -- how old is he there, Michael?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "He's about 9 or 10 there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Katherine", "Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Did he teach himself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "He taught himself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Was he always painting secretly without people really being aware of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "A bit of escape, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "And this collection, how many pieces are there in it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Well, I have -- we have 98 pieces.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Why did he like drawing or painting chairs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "He just had an obsession of chairs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Are they showing it on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "I mean if you had your time again, would you want the kids, especially Michael, to go into that crazy world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, to a certain extent.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Did he -- did he have to be that tough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "ACKSON: I didn't think he was too tough, but in -- back in those days everybody raised their children about the same.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Do you think that the world has gone a bit soft in terms of discipline?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "I think it's gone a bit too soft.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "The bible tells us the world will be destroyed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "When you look at America, modern America now, where do you think people are going wrong especially in bringing up children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNP", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well, I think society is sometimes is the fault of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "What are the parents to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "I mean it's interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "How did you feel as his mother?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Katherine"]}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Why are they doing this to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Just hold that thought for a moment, Katherine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "The rest of the world may not see this in the innocent way that you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "I've talked to him about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "I mean do you think that all the drugs he was taking for the anxiety, for the lack of sleep, the painkillers and so on, was it all connected, do you think, in the end to the pressure that he felt and the tension and the stress?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "You know what, I think a lot of that was exaggerated about the different things that he was taking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "What do you think, as his mother, caused his death?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Did you ever meet Conrad Murray?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Never met him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Has he ever tried to contact you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "He's never written to you or anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Will you ever get over this, Katherine, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Katherine"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "What do you think when you think of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "I just miss him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "It's so unnatural, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "How did you think he was in the buildup to his death physically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "You know, we have a trial going on and I'd rather not say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "Were you concerned about him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Do you feel that there were bad people around him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "It was all about money, you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "How are they getting along?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "They're getting along very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "His grades are so good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Do you see the spirit of Michael in them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Paris"]}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "If they want to go into show business?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Yes, Paris does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "Do you feel pleased about that or concerned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "Well, I'm pleased and I'm concerned at the same time because I didn't -- I don't think that Michael would wanted her to be out there this soon.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "I mean how talented are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "VBN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "She's very good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "How do you think they have coped with losing their father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "You know, I don't think that they act like normal children.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Were you concerned about him as a friend?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Well, his enthusiasm to succeed brought all the strength out in him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Were you concerned as a friend of his about what was possibly going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "Well, during the time that he was pretty much studying to do these concerts, I had very little contact with him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Katherine, what would you like Michael's legacy to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "I know he'll be remembered as the artist he was.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "You mean the scenes from Ethiopia and places in Africa with the starving young children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Starving young children with the big bellies.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ethiopia", "Africa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ":", "CC", "JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "What do you think is the biggest misconception about Michael for people who didn't know him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "The things that were coming out, the things that media -- and most people believe what they hear and what they read.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Like what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Like they were saying he was molesting young boys and other things that he was doing, that he might have been on painkillers, things like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Do you think it is even remotely possibly that he could have done anything inappropriate with a young boy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "No way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Is that how you felt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "You know, Michael, he was one of my younger children.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "Did that scare you, that level of fame?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "No, not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "How often would you talk to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "I talked to him at least twice a month and sometimes more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Did you feel you had a very close relationship?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Do you feel he confided in you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Yes, he did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Did you ever hope that he would find true love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "You know, I always thought about that, but Michael seemed happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Did you feel that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "I -- I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Would he try stuff out with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Yes, he played most of the things he had.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "If you said Michael, I don't really like that one, would he drop it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CD", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 532, "question": "What was your favorite of all his songs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "\"Man In The Mirror.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "That's one of my favorites.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Why \"Man In The Mirror\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Well, it was a message of greatness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Was Michael happy in the end, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "I felt he was happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "That's good to hear, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "It's good to hear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "How did that make you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "It made me feel good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "One is what are you going to do with this art?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBZ", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Well, Michael spent a good part of 25 years making this art.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "And they're going to want to know if they can get ahold them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "Well, Michael always wanted to exhibit his art.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "It's based on the Prince Albert Monument in London?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "Michael and I went around that monument.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Albert Monument"], "LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", ":", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Is this going to get built?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "Yes, because we can sell his art and build his -- even though it's a monument for where people -- he wanted people to get married, it's a monument to his love of life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Las Vegas"]}, "docId": "120514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Where will it go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "At the time, he was thinking Las Vegas.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]